Chiranjibi Pandey

Cell No.: 9849184825

Email: chiranjibipandey9@gmail.com

LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/chiranjibi-pandey-8090b0146

CAREER OBJECTIVE

To be a part of an organization where I can grow in terms of knowledge, skills and attitude and put to an effective use my analytical abilities and professional competence in the areas of accounting and auditing, so as to align self-development with organizational development.

PERSONAL PROFILE

A dynamic, resourceful and energetic chartered accountant experienced in providing full financial, administrative and office management support to work colleagues in a busy office environment. Having a proactive and flexible approach and able to work autonomously taking ownership of all aspects of a task or project.

CAREER HISTORY

Assistant Audit Manager- July 2017- Present
 Assistant Audit Manager – October 2015- September 2016

 Article Trainee - September 2012 – September 2015
 NK Sharma & Company
 Chartered Accountants

> General Experience

- Manage and supervise the execution of assurance and advisory engagements of various client
- Participation in preparing audit plans, programs and procedures
- Understanding the clients business and recognizing the risk factors
- Devising audit procedures to mitigate the recognized risks
- Monitor team's progress against the plan and alter it when needed and motivate the team members to achieve the targets.

Works Carried Out:

- Statutory Audit of Nepal Electricity Authority for FY 2073/74
- Statutory Audit of Rastriya Banijya Bank and Internal audit of development banks (International Development Bank Ltd. and Araniko Development Bank Ltd.)

PERSONAL DETAILS

Gender: Male Nationality: Nepali Marital Status: Single

DOB: 24th April 1990

Email: chiranjibipandey9@gmail.com

Cell: 9849184825

Address:

Temporary: Satungal-10, Chandragiri Kathmandu Permanent: Birghaarchale-04,

Syangja

PERSONAL SKILLS

- -Ability to work in a team environment
- -Initiative and desire to excel
- -Capability to supervise the work of others
- -Time management
- -Reliable & trustworthy
- -Multi-tasking

- Loan Portfolio Audit of Sana Kishan Bank Ltd. on behalf of ADB
- Statutory Audit/ Tax audit of NLIC
- Statutory audit/ Tax audit of Chilime Hydropower Company
- Statutory Audit of CDS and Clearing Ltd. for 2 fiscal years
- Funds Flow Tracking Survey of Department of Education on behalf of ADB
- Fiduciary Risk Review of Department of Health Services (NHSP II) on behalf of World Bank
- Fiduciary Risk Review of Skill Development Project (SDP) on behalf of ADB
- Special purpose audit of INGO/NGOs
- Micro assessment of Government Agencies (DDCs, DHOs, Departments and Ministries) and NGOs on behalf of UNICEF/UNDP
- Statutory Audit of UNDP- Nationally Executed (NEX) projects
- Statutory Audit of Small Grant Projects (SGPs) on behalf of UNDP
- Audit of NPTF and different NGAs on behalf of GIZ
- Special Audit of Nepal Scouts (FNPP) on behalf of Finland Embassy for 2 years
- Fixed Assets Verification on behalf of UNICEF
- Spot Check of different NGOs/projects funded by UNDP
- 2. Assistant Manager- Accounts/Finance-Nov 2016- till date

Flash Freight Logistics Pvt. Ltd.

Pulchowk, Lalitpur

> General Experience

- Responsible for smooth operation of Finance Department and ensuring up-to-date accounting system.
- Preparation of periodic and annual financial statements in compliance to the Nepal Financial Reporting Standards.
- Correspondence with overseas and domestic service providers/ customers and providing financial data to management for decision making.
- Submission of advance tax and advance tax return, completion of e-TDS process and overall matters related to taxation.
- Ensuring timely statutory reporting to the Office of Company Registrar and NRB.
- Assisting the auditors in completion of audit.
- Supervision of the work of team members; providing targets and monitoring performance.

KEY SKILLS AND COMPETENCIES

> Trainings

Year	Particulars		
2016	General Management and Communication Skills (GMCS) training organized by ICAN		
2014	Training on Income Tax conducted on behalf of International agency		
	- Attended as well as facilitated as a Co-trainer and assisted in preparation of training materials		
2013	Information Technology (IT) Training		
(100 hrs)	- Basic working knowledge		
	- Word, Excel, Power point		
	- Database management		
	- Internet & Networking		

- Use of CAATS as audit tools

Language skills

✓ Fluency in speaking and writing in English, Nepali and Hindi.

> Other skills

- ✓ In depth knowledge on Accounting, Finance, Costing, Business Laws and Taxation.
- ✓ Knowledge on the use of accounting software such as Tally, PUMORI and ATLAS.

EDUCATION:

PROFESSIONAL QUALIFICATIONS

Chartered Accountant

Institute of Chartered Accountants of Nepal (ICAN)

Membership No.: 1011

ACADEMIC QUALIFICATIONS

Level	Board/College	Passed Year	Percentage (%)
Master's in Business Studies (Tribhuwan University	2016	❖ Refer below
MBS)			
Bachelors in Business Studies	Tribhuvan University/	2013	65.57
(BBS)	Shankar Dev Campus		First Division
High School	Higher Secondary Education Board	2008	76.6
(Intermediate (+2))	/ KIST College		Distinction
School (SLC)	Government of Nepal/	2006	86.5
	Gyankunj Higher Secondary School		Distinction

As per the Directory of Recognition and Equivalence of Educational Qualifications, Volume III (published by TU), CA after Bachelor's degree is given Masters Equivalent in Relevant Subject by TU.

Awards and Achievements

✓ Received award from Shankar Dev Campus for standing first in BBS 1st year by securing 70%

REFERENCES:

Mr. Nanda Kishor Sharma, FCA, CPFA

Principal

NK Sharma & Company, Chartered Accountants

Email: nksco@ntc.net.np

Cell no.: 9851034277

Mr. Dipendra Subedi, CA

Deputy Director

Nepal Airlines Corporation

Email: dipssubedi10@yahoo.com

Cell no.: 9851169753

Certification:

I certify that to the best of my knowledge and belief, information provided above correctly describes my qualifications and my experience.